today Charlie Brown arrived here in Guarujá
that's right
we are here in Guarujá with us
trickery
it's good for you,
right?
Charlie Brown
here on the spectrum
points of sale we go in caruda see what happens
it's us bro
relying on our potential and march
has no other form
the strategy i make
to start opening point of sale mano
is not to talk about business at the first moment
and yes arrive at the houses
show
know our product
the brand's intention is to position itself
is on
oh how crazy there oh
what is your cousin name
cyan falls there
soft hour bro
we open Charlie Brown
a Brown in the shape of a skate wheel
thank you brother
let a charlie browning you meet
first
browning with skate wheel shape
it has an original pink filling
this one is Charlie Browning
Charlie Browning
knows
for a walk
we are together there brother
bursts
walk
so if you're interested,
just call us
good cheat there we are responsible
no but we made a noise
the guys freaked out
hope you suddenly get our phone to play bora
caraca look there
did you see this
this one does not
our Face
then guys call bro
we are here on the coal that we have just closed
Guarujá's first point
can pull over bro
on the coal has Charlie Brown
the descent
hand truncheon
I really wanted to stick this house here
thanks for the opportunity
tamo together
but there will be a time
that we will be very limited
with this
I'm here in Guarujá
I deliver a box
then the guy from Santos calls
Oh I need to make the replacement
think of a way to climb faster and farther
sell the chevas and buy a bus
have to sell